quizurself.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy - QuizurselfQuizurself

Thank you for visiting our website located at www.quizurself.com (the “Site”). The Site is an Internet property of Matomy Media Group, Inc. (“Company,” “we,” “our” or “us”). Company has created this Website Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) in order to disclose our information gathering, use and dissemination practices. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you view certain content, links and other marketing material made available on the Site (“Site Content”).

This Privacy Policy only governs your use of the Site Offerings. The privacy practices associated with your use of third party websites are set forth in such third party’s privacy policy (“Third Party Privacy Policy”). Company has no control over, and is not responsible for, the privacy practices of any third party whose links may be on our Site or within our Site Content. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning set forth in Terms and Conditions (“Terms and Conditions”). **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN THEIR ENTIRETY, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE OFFERINGS.**

**Personal Information Collected**

Company does not collect your personal information in connection with your use of the Site Content. The only circumstances in which Company collects your personal information is where you provide feedback, comments and/or otherwise contact Company.

**Sharing and Use of Personal Information**

We will never sell, rent, exchange or barter your personal information to or with any third party for financial gain or marketing purposes. Where you request to be contacted by us, we use the personal information that you make available to respond to your questions or comments.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Company reserves the right to release current or past personal information: (a) in the event that we believe that the Site Content is, or has been, used in violation of the Agreement or to commit unlawful acts; (b) if the information is subpoenaed; provided, however, that, where permitted by applicable law, we shall provide you with e-mail notice, and opportunity to challenge the subpoena, prior to disclosure of any personal information pursuant to a subpoena; or (c) if we are sold, merge with a third party, are acquired or are the subject of bankruptcy proceedings; provided, however, that if Company is involved in a bankruptcy proceeding, merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices that you may have regarding your personal information.

**Non-Personal Information Collection and Use**

_IP Addresses/Browser Type_  
We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the pages of the Site. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon, AT&T). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site Offerings and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze usage of the Site Offerings, as well as to offer you products and services.

_Cookies_  
When an end-user visits the Site, we send a cookie and/or gif file (“Cookie”) to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable end-user’s Internet browser. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience on the Site. To find out more about Cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where an end-user rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use the Site Offerings; provided, however, that certain functions of the Site Offerings may be impaired or rendered inoperable if the use of Cookies is disabled. We reserve the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely.

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the Site and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Company does not control the use of such technology and Company has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you.

_Aggregate Data_  
Company reserves the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about Company end-users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage or other characteristics of Company end-users as a group, without disclosing personally identifiable information.

_Behavioral Tracking/Do-Not-Track_  
Company uses Cookies, pixels and other tracking technology on the Site for purposes of tracking end-users’ activities after they leave the Site. Company uses these Cookies to target applicable end-users with advertisements regarding Site Offerings and other products and/or services that Company thinks may be of interest to applicable end-users. In addition, third parties such as Google® may engage in a similar form of behavioral tracking of end-users that visit the Site. End-users may be able to disable some, but not all, of this tracking activity by utilizing the “Do Not Track” setting or similar options within most major Internet browsers. To the greatest extent permissible under applicable law, we are not responsible for the tracking practices of third parties in connection with the Site.

**Other Websites**

The Site may contain links to third-party owned and/or operated websites. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of these third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Company has no responsibility or liability relating to them.

**Security**

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our end-users’ personal information. When end-users make personal information available to us, their personal information is protected both online and offline (to the extent that we maintain any personal information offline). The privacy of your personal information is very important to us.

Access to your personal information is strictly limited, and we take reasonable measures to ensure that your personal information is not accessible to the public. The servers that we store personal information on are kept in a secure physical environment. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no storage facility, technology, software, security protocols or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

Computer hackers that circumvent our security measures may gain access to certain portions of your personal information, and technological bugs, errors and glitches may cause inadvertent disclosures of your personal information; provided, however, that any attempt to breach the security of the network, our servers, databases or other hardware or software may constitute a crime punishable by law. For the reasons mentioned above, we cannot warrant that your personal information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through the Site is at your own risk.

All of our end-users’ personal information is restricted in our offices. Only employees or third party agents who need the personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all end-user personal information. Employees not adhering to our Company policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

**Minors**

Visitors under eighteen (18) years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their personal information at the Site. Company does not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under eighteen (18) years of age. Company encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

**Opt-Out**

To opt-out of receiving e-mail communications from us, you can follow the instructions at the end of the applicable e-mail message or e-mail us at: great_content@mail.com.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for purposes of communicating information relating to any inquiry or request made by you. To opt-out of receiving inquiry response-related messages from Company, you must cease submitting inquiries.

**Identifying, Deleting and Updating Your Information**

At your request, we will inform you of what personal information we have on file for you. In addition, at your request, we will remove and/or modify the personal information that you have provided to us, or that we have collected. You may do so by contacting us via e-mail at: great_content@mail.com; provided, however, that we ask individuals to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Please be advised that, after you delete your personal information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Company reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice on the Site that we are changing this Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personally identifiable information changes, Company will notify end-users by: (a) sending the modified policy to our end-users via email; and/or (b) by any other reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner, and we will only use your information in this different manner where you opt-in to such use.

**Contacting the Site**

We listen to or read, as applicable, every message sent to us and endeavor to reply promptly to each one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of Company, please feel free to e-mail us at: great_content@mail.com; call us at: +972.77.360.6152; or send correspondence to the following address: 6 Hanechoshet St. Tel-Aviv, 69710 Israel.
